var questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Which neurotransmitter has the scientific name, 5-hydroxytryptamine?\n (a) Serotonin\n (b) Dopamine\n (c) Acetylcholine\n (d) Epinephrine",
        answer: "a"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which neurotransmitter is known as the “feel-good neurotransmitter”?\n (a) Acetylcholine\n (b) Epinephrine\n (c) Serotonin\n (d) Dopamine",
        answer: "d"
    },
    {
        prompt: "The neurotransmitter ________ can block the sensation of pain.\n (a) Serotonin\n (b) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)\n (c) Dopamine\n (d) Acetylcholine",
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        prompt: "This neurotransmitter is largely responsible for motivation and reward.\n (a) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)\n (b) Dopamine\n (c) Acetylcholine\n (d) Serotonin",
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What neurotransmitter is responsible for activating muscle movement?\n (a) Acetylcholine\n (b) Dopamine\n (c) Epinephrine\n (d) Serotonin",
        answer: "a"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which neurotransmitter makes us more alert?\n (a) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)\n (b) Serotonin\n (c) Dopamine\n (d) Serotonin",
        answer: "a"
    },
    {
        prompt: "This neurotransmitter controls the dilation of blood vessels.\n (a) Dopamine\n (b) Acetylcholine\n (c) Serotonin\n (d) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)",
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What neurotransmitter is most responsible for mood?\n (a) Dopamine\n (b) Serotonin\n (c) Acetylcholine\n (d) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)",
        answer: "b"
    },
    {
        prompt: "This neurotransmitter can stop allergic reactions.\n (a) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)\n (b) Acetylcholine\n (c) Dopamine\n (d) Serotonin",
        answer: "a"
    },
    {
        prompt: "The neurotransmitter __________ can restart a stopped heart!\n (a) Acetylcholine\n (b) Serotonin\n (c) Dopamine\n (d) Adrenaline (Epinephrine)",
        answer: "d"
    }
];